Charlie, you got me.
>> Yes, I do.
>> All right, go ahead, John.
>> Hey, Leo. Welcome to Washington.
Congrats. What do you What do you feel
that you most bring to the Commanders?
>> Um, you know, I've I've said it before,
I'll say it again. You know, I bring I
bring violence, physicality. Um, you
know, game day, I'm bringing that
energy, that juice. I'm ready to get
these guys rolling. you know, not that
they need it anymore, but you know, I'm
ready to uplift any way that I can,
supplement any way I can, and uh again,
get this rolling.
>> So, where do you feel like your game
took a big jump last year that, you
know, that is shows where you're headed?
Maybe.
>> Um, you know, it's just continuing to
build um every aspect of the game. You
know, I can I can really be anywhere,
you know, whether it's on the line, um
off the ball, you know, defending a
pass, down the field. Um it's it's just
really kind of building off things. um
eyes are continuing to progress and you
know make plays into coverage as well.
Um so it's not only defending the run um
but being able to drop back, cover a
tight end, what whatever um you know
coach asked me to do, I'm ready to do
it.
>> Thank you,
>> Nikki.
>> Hi Leo. Um what intrigued you about
Washington? Why did you want to come
here?
>> Um you know, it's it's it's different.
You know, I just I've heard great things
um just about the coaching staff,
especially recently. Um, you know, I got
former former teammates uh here that are
on the team now and just the way they
describe the coaching staff, just the
kind of the vibe, um, just the way it is
and it guys are excited here. Um, guys
are excited, um, to show up to the
building. Uh, guys are loving football
here. Um, it's just it's just so many
good things. I' I really haven't heard a
bad thing about, you know, the culture
that they're building here, that we're
building here. Um, so I'm just excited
to be part of it.
>> So, you did reach out to guys like WY
and Aligradi and the other chief. Yeah.
Yeah. It's so it's nice having those
resources and um you know it's you know
I other people that kind of knew certain
things and it's just trying to pull from
every resource and I I didn't hear
anything you know negative in terms of
just the people being around and that's
that's a huge part of it, right? It's
it's just do you want to like show up
and obviously everybody wants to play
football but do you want to show up and
do you know the boring the quoteunquote
boring things every single day? Like do
you want to be excited for it? And um
you know it helps just being around so
many so many cool people.
David Aldridge,
>> welcome to DC, man.
>> Appreciate you. H
>> how did uh what did the coaches say to
you about how they plan to use you or
what they want how they want to use you
next year?
>> Yeah, you know, just like I mentioned,
like I'm I'm a versatile player. Um you
know, that's what I pride myself in
being. You know, um as I progressed to
my when I first came to the league, you
know, I was off linebacker at Wisconsin.
never really been on the line, but um
you know, and I I I wasn't asked to do
much a whole lot in coverage in college
and stuff. So, as I got in the league,
I'm slowly progressing. You know, I can
play anywhere, like I said, on the line,
off the ball. So, it's you know, maybe
moving around a little bit, maybe
staying in a spot more than the more
than others, but you know, it's kind of
fun just to hear their plan like, okay,
you know, we just want to unleash you um
you know, in the middle blitzing um
doing what we can there and just kind of
having that, you know, freedom in their
in their mind um to just do go out and
play, make plays.
you I mean obviously you're in a very
you come from a very successful program
in Kansas City. I just wonder like to
leave that to come to a team that's kind
of building like what was kind of like
the special sauce that made you willing
to take the jump like you could have
stayed in Kansas City forever. You know
what I mean? Like you could have been
great there for a long time.
>> Yeah, obviously you know records you
know this past year the team like with
the Chiefs we didn't have a great
record. um you know um here we probably
didn't meet expectations you know so
it's I just know that we got a bunch of
great players in the building that are
capable of winning um we got a we got a
staff front office coaches everybody
involved it's like the energy the
culture that they have were capable of
having a great record pushing you know
in the playoffs so um you know I didn't
I didn't look at records I looked at you
know where where can I thrive where can
I thrive you know as a team as well like
where are we going to thrive and um you
know this this place just stuck out a
for sure.
>> Thank you,
>> David Harrison.
>> Hey, Leo. Welcome to Washington.
Congratulations on your new contract.
Um, coming from the defense you did in
Kansas City, looking at the defense that
you're joining in Washington, what from
your previous experiences gives you
confidence that this is the right fit
for you? Um, you know, it's it's being
able to play like I I experimented a
little bit, not fully in games, but, you
know, I had my moments in games just,
you know, playing off Mike, um, weak
side linebacker and our nickel package.
Um, so I've I'm so used to and as the
years went on, I got four years in the
league under my belt, just being able to
play different positions. Um, you know,
I got a lot of reps in different
positions in training camp, even alone.
Um, you know, Coach Sp, you know,
putting me in different spots and
sometimes at first uncomfortable and
I've just been really willing, um, to,
you know, do whatever the coach asks in
terms of, you know, play in a different
spot even if I am uncomfortable at
first. So, I just feel like I can just
be on the line, you know, be at, you
know, even a the three tech knows
sometimes, you know, whatever whatever
they ask, you know, I'm I'm just willing
to do it. I've been in those
uncomfortable positions.
>> Yeah. And the one of the new rules is
this your free agency teams were allowed
to call players for up to an hour and
talk directly to you guys. Did
Washington or any other teams take
advantage of that rule with you? And if
so, how did that kind of uh I don't
know, how did that kind of impact
things?
>> Um yeah, no, I definitely I definitely
took advantage of that with them. Um you
know, they were really really kind and
really you know, I just love like the
the interest and like the enthusiasm
about it. um you know with coming from
them and just just I mean I've already
heard great things about the coaching
staff, Coach Quinn, um AP and everything
and uh Coach Jones like so it was it was
really cool just to actually talk to
them and you know like just see like
actually see them and hear them and like
oh wow these guys these guys are legit.
These are really cool guys and kind um
you know enthusiastic, passionate, like
you name it. Um so it's cool to kind of
you know be able to see it in person.
>> Thank you. Can I ask who you talked to
in that conversation? Um, you know, just
the the guys I mentioned, you know, I I
talked to Coach Quinn, uh, uh, Donte,
uh, you know, Coach Jones. Uh, so it's
just those guys, you know, it's just
hearing that and the culture that you
can hear it, you know, in their voices
and just the excitement. Um, it was
pretty special.
>> Awesome. Thank you.
>> Thank you,
>> Donna.
>> Hey, Leo. Welcome to Washington. Hey,
thank you.
>> You talked a little while ago about just
thriving. Um, and I know you played
special teams, too. So, how do you see
yourself thriving the most as you come
to Washington and be a part of this
defense?
>> Um, you know, I look back to my
Wisconsin days. You know, I I really
thrived off the ball. Um, you know,
playing kind of seeing the middle, being
in the middle and seeing a lot of things
and be able to make plays anywhere. Um,
but, you know, now I have those reps
under my belt, you know, playing Sam
linebacker too, um, or off the ball,
weak side linebacker as a buck we call
it. And uh just having that experience
and then going full special teams, you
know, as well, like I can I can make big
plays in special teams if I need to, you
know, field goal block, you know,
different different things, make plays
in kickoff, whatever it is, you know,
I'm I'm excited to just be out there um
you know, take advantage of things and
um I just love playing football. So, you
know, if I get on that field a little
more, whatever it is. and and one of
your teammates, former teammates with
the chiefs with the Kansas City Chiefs
talked about that the commanders are
getting a strong addition with you. Uh
he gave you a lot of pats on the back.
Uh could you talk a little bit about
that that confidence as he had in you
and then also what you want to the
brotherhood to know about you?
>> Are you talking about uh Charles?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Chuck. Uh no, he's he's
awesome. As soon as I heard that, I was
I was, you know, I was revved up. Uh,
you know, to have somebody like him, um,
you know, a vet guy that's, you know,
known success and, you know, he's made a
lot of plays, too. And, um, it it's just
special to be able to have that
connection. And, you know, I already
have, um, Wy Aligretti, um, you know,
even coach Jones, you know, he he played
at Wisconsin um, a little bit uh, uh, or
he played at Wisconsin. So, it's cool
having that, you know, it's it's
something special. And either way, we're
going to build relationships with
anybody, but you know, it's cool having
that brotherhood.
>> Thanks.
>> Thank you,
>> Ben.
>> Hey, Leah, welcome to town.
>> Thank you.
>> Um, your athleticism at from like from
when you came into the league at the
combine is pretty significant, notable,
uh, across the board. Being a being a
great athlete is one thing, but
translated in that production is
another. How is how have you used some
of your athletic traits specifically to
help you uh in the league?
>> Yeah, I mean I think like my big thing,
you know, at Wisconsin like I was
talking about and you know in the league
it's like getting downhill is really a
strong suit of mine. Um you know beyond
the line of scrimmage or even just like
attacking blocks from a down tight end
or a tackle or a double team even from a
a tackle guard center. Um you know my
strong suit is strength. You know I do
well acceleration just getting downhill
like I said. So, um, I can use those to
my advantage, you know, whether it's
striking, getting a long arm, extending.
Um, so I've just had a lot of success
and I've I've continued to build upon it
and get better at, um, you know,
especially defending the running,
getting downhill, um, breaking on
passes. I've continually gotten better
at that area as well.
>> And as you're preparing to make a huge
decision, where do you want to go? How
did you approach Washington's defensive